http://www.ctd.northwestern.edu/ctd-privacy-policy

CTD Privacy Policy
Northwestern University and Center for Talent Development (CTD) are committed to protecting the privacy rights of any child in accordance with applicable laws.
Accordingly, the following policy governs CTD’s treatment of students’ educational records in connection with its programs.
Information CTD Collects
CTD gathers two types of information: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, address, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, parent name, financial information for the purposes of billing and payment and credit card information for payment. Non-personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, gender, name of school the student attends, grade in school, ethnic background (optional), birth date, qualifying test scores and test date and center, primary language spoken at home (optional), household size and income (optional), course choice, and program location.
How Information Is Treated
Unless required by law, needed for essential services as part of an approved agreement (e.g. Schoology, etc.), or authorized by parent(s) or legal guardian(s), CTD does not disclose personally identifiable information about its students to third parties. If CTD receives appropriate consent the center may provide names and addresses of individuals to third parties that have programs geared toward academically talented youth.
Non-personally identifiable information collected may be used for research purposes. Non-personally identifiable or deidentified student information may be shared with third-party vendors for research or program related services.
E-mail Notifications
As program participants, students and families receive e-mail notifications regarding Center for Talent Development programs and services. If you do not wish to receive these e-mail messages, you may always unsubscribe through the unsubscribe option in the message footer. Please note that opting out of marketing emails will not prevent you from receiving nonmarketing notifications about CTD programs in which you or your child are active.
Footer Links 1
About CTD
Programs
Enrollment
Resources
Explore Courses
Footer Links 2
For Educators
Copyright 2014 Northwestern University Center for Talent Development
Copyright Menu
Policy
Privacy
Sitemap
